/*global angular */

angular.module('mathSkills').value('data1_2', {
    title: '1.2 Standard Notation of Whole Numbers',
    path: '1.2-standard-notation-of-whole-numbers',
    children: [{
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write fifty-eight in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{58}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{Fifty-eight in number notation is 58}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write one hundred seventy-four in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{174}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{One hundred seventy-four in number notation is 174}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write three hundred thirty-six in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{336}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{Three hundred thirty-six in number notation is 336}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write three thousand, three hundred eighty-six in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{3386}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{3,386}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write fifty thousand, nine hundred fifty-seven in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{50957}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{50,957}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write four hundred one in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{401}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{Four hundred one in number notation is 401}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write seven thousand, seven hundred nineteen in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{7719}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{7,719}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write seventy-three thousand, one hundred seventy-eight in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{73178}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{73,178}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write one hundred twenty-six in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{126}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{126}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, {
        title: 'Words to Number',
        children: [{
            title: 'Main Answer',
            children: [{
                problem: '\\str{Write seven thousand, seven hundred forty-eight in number notation}',
                answer: '\\input{7748}',
                controls: {
                    "checkAnswer": true,
                    "help": '\\str{7,748}'
                }
            }]
        }]
    }, ]
});
